{
    "true-false": [
        {
            "question": "The cows are red",
            "answer": "false"
        },
        {
            "question": "The anime industry is from Japan",
            "answer": "true"
        },
        {
            "question": "2 * 4 = 8",
            "answer": "true"
        },
        {
            "question": "Maths are not a science",
            "answer": "false"
        },
        {
            "question": "The Legend of Zelda is a videogame",
            "answer": "true"
        },
        {
            "question": "Unicorn is the national animal of scotland",
            "answer": "true"
        },
        {
            "question": "An apple is a fruit",
            "answer": "true"
        },
        {
            "question": "The diameter of the earth is 12.742 km",
            "answer": "true"
        },
        {
            "question": "1 + 1 + 1 + 1 + 1 + 1 + 1 = 8",
            "answer": "false"
        },
        {
            "question": "World War I started at 1912",
            "answer": "false"
        }
    ],
    "slider": [
        {
            "question": "In soccer, how many goals are a Hat Trick?",
            "min": 1,
            "max": 11,
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "A lustrum has _ years",
            "min": 0,
            "max": 10,
            "answer": 5
        },
        {
            "question": "What number on the P.T. does nitrogen occupy?",
            "min": 1,
            "max": 11,
            "answer": 7
        },
        {
            "question": "30/6+5*2",
            "min": 5,
            "max": 15,
            "answer": 15
        },
        {
            "question": "How many Rings of Power exist?",
            "min": 10,
            "max": 20,
            "answer": 20
        },
        {
            "question": "The Pikachu number in Pokedex is...",
            "min": 22,
            "max": 32,
            "answer": 25
        },
        {
            "question": "At what age do you retire?",
            "min": 60,
            "max": 70,
            "answer": 67
        },
        {
            "question": "How many swords does Zoro from One Piece wield?",
            "min": 1,
            "max": 11,
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "There are _ Dark souls games",
            "min": 0,
            "max": 10,
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Sound travels at _ meters per second",
            "min": 340,
            "max": 350,
            "answer": 343
        }
    ]
}